Giordi Fungula

Software Developer

Enthusiastic technical professional with complete understanding of entire software development lifecycle. Highly trained in Javascript and Web Development and known for having talents in React and Back End Development. Experienced Software Developer with over 2 years of experience in the Software Industry. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

Work History

2020-05 -Current

Software Engineer

Symbionix, Cape Town, Western Cape

- Applied latest emerging technology, software and project application trends to update and maintain site applicability.
- Collaborated with team members to establish project goals, projections and milestones.
- Develop API and UI features as per client demands and needs.

2019-03 -2020-05

Mentor and Instructor

Hyperion Development, Cape Town, Western Cape

- Taught classes and presented self-help or information sessions on subjects related to education and career planning.
- Developed classroom guidelines and assignment rules to communicate expectations.
- Worked one-on-one with students and student teachers to increase overall classroom effectiveness.

Education

2021-02 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer And Information Sciences

University of South Africa - Cape Town (Online)

Contact

Address

Cape Town, WC, 7945

Phone

084 063 0877

E-mail

jodi.fungula@gmail.com

Skills

Web-based software engineering

Database management software

Code reviews

Software Development

Programming

JavaScript

React

HTML

Languages

English

Lingala

Basic French